>> TONIGHT, THE DRAMATIC SEASON
FINALE OF "THE BACHELORETTE"
BEGINS.
>> I'M FREAKING OUT.
IT'S REALLY, REALLY HARD.
>> FIRST, IT'S A ROSE CEREMONY
LIKE NO OTHER.
THREE MEN REMAIN:
PETER, JED, AND TYLER.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW I TELL
SOMEBODY THEY'RE NOT ENOUGH.
>> WHO WILL HANNAH SEND HOME?
>> [CRYING]
>> AND NOW...
>> [BLEEP] ME.
THIS IS WHY YOU DON'T DATE TWO
PEOPLE AT THE SAME TIME.
>> HOW WILL HANNAH DECIDE
BETWEEN THE MEN SHE LOVES?
>> I CAN TELL YOU HAVE CONCERNS
SO JUST -- WILL YOU JUST SAY
THEM?
>> I DON'T WANT YOU TO SETTLE
FOR ANYTHING.
AND THAT'S AS HONEST AS I CAN
BE.
>> I WANT SOMEBODY THAT WOULD
LOVE YOU LIKE I KNOW YOU SHOULD
BE LOVED.
♪
>> I CAN'T DO THIS.
I --
CAN YOU STOP THE CAR?
[GRUNTS]
I REALLY CAN'T DO THIS.
>> WHAT HAPPENS NEXT IS LIKE
NOTHING YOU'VE SEEN BEFORE.
>> I JUST FEEL LIKE THIS
EXPERIENCE HAS BEEN TAKEN AWAY
FROM ME.
ALL OF THE SCARS THAT HAVE BEEN
ON MY HEART IS BECAUSE OF PEOPLE
NOT BEING HONEST WITH ME.
>> IT'S THE SHOCKING TWO-NIGHT
TELEVISION EVENT OF THE SUMMER.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF I WANT THIS.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> IT'S LIVE, AND IT ALL STARTS
RIGHT NOW.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
♪
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU.
WELCOME, BACHELOR NATION, I AM
CHRIS HARRISON.
WELL, WE HAVE FINALLY ARRIVED.
HANNAH'S DRAMATIC JOURNEY TO
FIND LOVE WITH ITS MANY DRAMATIC
AND SHOCKING TWISTS IS ABOUT TO
COME TO AN END, BUT WHAT
PROMISES TO HAPPEN OVER THE NEXT
TWO NIGHTS IS LIKE NOTHING YOU
HAVE EXPERIENCED BEFORE, AND
TRUTHFULLY, EVEN I DON'T REALLY
KNOW WHAT'S GOING TO TAKE PLACE
ON THIS STAGE OF LIFE.
WILL HANNAH FIND LOVE?
WILL SHE GET ENGAGED?
AND IF SHE DOES, WILL HER STORY
HAVE A HAPPY ENDING?
MAYBE NOT.
WE ARE ALL IN FOR A WILD RIDE.
BUT FIRST, THREE MEN ARE
STANDING AT A ROSE CEREMONY IN
GREECE RECOVERING FROM THEIR
SHOCKING CONFRONTATION WITH LUKE
P., TYLER, PETER, AND JED ARE
ALL IN LOVE WITH HANNAH AND
READY TO ACCEPT HER ROSE, SO WHO
WILL HANNAH SEND HOME?
LET'S FIND OUT.
[GULLS SQUAWKING]
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> WHY WAS HE WAS EVEN HERE?
>> THAT'S SUCH A LUKE THING TO
DO.
>> BUT IT WAS SUCH A LUKE THING.
SHE HANDLED IT LIKE A CHAMP.
>> SHE DID.
IT WAS A HOME RUN.
>> SHE HANDLED IT LIKE A BADASS.
>> I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT TO DO
RIGHT NOW.
>> WE STILL HAVE A ROSE
CEREMONY.
♪
>> THIS WEEK HAS BEEN CRAZY
INSANE.
I SENT LUKE HOME.
>> PUT THIS BACK.
>> AND I HAVE NO REGRETS.
BUT NOW I HAVE A BIG DECISION TO
MAKE, AND MY HEART HURTS.
I HAVE THREE MEN THAT I THINK I
COULD SPEND THE REST OF MY LIFE
WITH AND CAN SEE A FUTURE WITH.
WHICH FUTURE DO I WANT?
THIS HAS DEFINITELY BEEN THE
BIGGEST BATTLE OF MY HEART.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOING TO
HAPPEN.
I'VE PUT MY HEART ON THE LINE.
I'VE TOLD HER HOW I FEEL.
TO GET A ROSE TODAY, IT SHOWS ME
THAT WE'RE ONE STEP CLOSER TO
BEING ENGAGED AND THAT SHE WANTS
THAT TOO.
>> HANNAH IS EVERYTHING I'VE
EVER WANTED.
YOU HAVE TO HAVE THAT ONE IN A
MILLION CONNECTION WITH SOMEONE
TO REALLY MAKE THINGS WORK, AND
I REALLY DO BELIEVE THAT WE HAVE
THAT.
I DON'T WANT THIS TO EVER END.
>> I'VE NEVER FELT THIS
INTENSELY FOR SOMEONE.
I KNOW HANNAH AND I HAVE SO MUCH
POTENTIAL FOR THE MOST AMAZING
LIVES TOGETHER.
>> I 100% CAN SEE THIS WOMAN AS
MY WIFE.
LIKE, 100%.
[EXHALES]
IT'S A BIG DAY.
>> I HAVE THREE AMAZING MEN
STANDING IN FRONT OF ME, AND
THIS WEEK HAS BEEN AMAZING.
I, LIKE, STAND HERE AND FEEL SO
LUCKY TO BE SO LOVED.
AND KNOW THAT THIS IS SO HARD
FOR ME.
YOU'VE OPENED YOUR HEART TO ME,
YOUR FAMILIES.
YOU'VE BEEN VULNERABLE AND
HONEST AND OPEN, AND I JUST FEEL
SO BLESSED TO HAVE YOU ALL IN MY
LIFE.
BUT THERE IS AN END GAME FOR ME
IN THIS, AND I HAVE TO CONTINUE
TO MAKE THE HARD DECISIONS.
AND THAT MAKES THIS HARD FOR ME,
'CAUSE I'M NOT JUST BREAKING
SOMEBODY'S HEART, I'M BREAKING
MY HEART.
♪
JED.
JED, WILL YOU ACCEPT THIS ROSE?
>> I WILL.
>> THANK YOU.
>> I REALLY DO LOVE
HANNAH BROWN, AND SHE REALLY
MEANS THE WORLD TO ME, AND IT
WOULD BE GUT-WRENCHING IF I
DIDN'T GET THAT ROSE.
>> I FEEL LIKE WE HAVE SUCH AN
AN UNBELIEVABLE, JUST PURE,
UNIQUE LOVE THAT I JUST -- LIKE,
I KNOW.
I KNOW THAT WE'RE MEANT TO BE
TOGETHER.
>> TYLER.
TYLER, WILL YOU ACCEPT THIS
ROSE?
>> ALWAYS, HANNAH.
YOU'RE AMAZING.
♪
>> PETER, I'M SORRY.
TAKE A MOMENT AND SAY YOUR
GOODBYES.
♪
>> HEY.
>> HI.
>> CAN I WALK YOU OUT?
>> YEAH.
>> [SNIFFLING]
OH, MY GOSH.
I JUST -- LIKE, EVERYTHING THAT
OUR RELATIONSHIP HAS BEEN HAS
BEEN PERFECT, AND IT HAS BEEN SO
EASY.
YOU'RE, LIKE, THE DREAM GUY
THAT -- I HAVE SAID THIS, LIKE,
EVERY TIME, LIKE, I WAS LITTLE,
I THINK I WAS, LIKE, PLAYING
WITH MY DOLLS, IF I LIKE, HAD MY
KEN DOLL, I FEEL LIKE YOU'RE
THAT.
YOU'RE THAT.
THERE'S -- IT'S JUST, LIKE,
NOTHING WRONG.
JUST NOT MINE --
>> I -- I GET THAT, AND --
>> AND THIS WEEK WAS --
>> YEAH.
IT WAS AMAZING.
I --
>> IT WAS AMAZING.
>> HANNAH, HONESTLY, LIKE, I --
GOD, I'M TRYING TO, LIKE, BE
STRONG RIGHT NOW, SO...
UM, YOU WILL TRULY, LIKE, ALWAYS
HAVE, LIKE, A PIECE OF MY HEART.
AND, LIKE, I TRULY MEAN THAT.
AND THIS, LIKE, THIS SUCKS RIGHT
NOW, AND THIS HURTS.
BUT I DON'T REGRET ANYTHING
ABOUT IT.
I TRULY DON'T.
♪
OKAY, LET'S --
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
♪
[CRYING]
BYE.
♪
>> [CRYING]
>> OH, THIS SUCKS.
I DID NOT SEE THAT COMING AT
ALL.
AND I'M NOT -- LIKE, I'M NOT MAD
AT HANNAH.
LIKE, I -- I'M REALLY NOT.
LIKE, I'M -- IT HURTS LIKE A
BITCH RIGHT NOW, BUT...
I'LL NEVER FORGET THIS JOURNEY.
HOW BEAUTIFUL IT WAS, LIKE, IN
SO MANY WAYS.
I FELL IN LOVE WITH HER.
AND I SWEAR, LIKE, I DON'T
REGRET -- I DON'T REGRET
ANYTHING.
♪
>> [CRYING]
>> I KNOW I HAVE A TON OF LOVE
TO GIVE, AND I THOUGHT IT WAS
HANNAH.
LIKE, I TRULY DID.
[SIGHS]
>> [CRYING]
>> WE ARE BACK DON'T LIVE IN OUR
LOS ANGELES STUDIO.
PETER IS WITH ME.
HE JUST WATCH THIS FOR THE FIRST
TIME ALONG WITH ALL OF YOU.
ARE YOU OKAY?
>> YEAH.
I WAS KIND OF DREADING HAVING TO
WATCH THAT BACK THIS ENTIRE TIME
FROM THE LAST, JUST, TWO MONTHS
OF THIS.
BUT, UH, YEAH, I'M OKAY.
>> I CAN TELL YOU WERE VERY MUCH
IN LOVE WITH HANNAH.
>> THERE'S NO DOUBT ABOUT THAT
AT ALL.
SHE WAS JUST HONESTLY THE MOST
AMAZING PERSON I'VE MET SO FAR
IN MY LIFE, AND I WAS JUST SO
GRATEFUL FOR ALL THOSE MEMORIES
THAT WE MADE AND BEING ABLE TO
FALL IN LOVE WITH HER.
>> YOU WERE HAVING TROUBLE
WATCHING THAT.
YOU TURNED YOUR HEAD AWAY AT
TIMES.
>> [SIGHS]
YEAH.
IT WASN'T EASY.
I REALLY FELT FOR HER, AND I HAD
NO DOUBT THAT IT WAS GOING TO BE
US IN THE END.
I REALLY DIDN'T.
[SIGHS]
SO, YEAH.
IT WAS TOUGH TO WATCH BACK.
>> SEEING THE TEARS IN YOUR
EYES, I LOOK AROUND THIS STUDIO
AUDIENCE, YOUR MOM, YOUR DAD,
YOUR BROTHER, BARBARA, PETER,
JACK, THEY ARE HERE, YOUR MOM
HAS GONE THROUGH A BOX OF
KLEENEX IS.
>> YEAH.
>> WE ALL FELL IN LOVE WITH YOUR
FAMILY ON YOUR HOME TOWN DAY.
WE KNOW WHERE YOU COME FROM.
>> YEAH.
>> BUT THIS IS A GOOD EXAMPLE
OF, IT'S NOT JUST YOU GOING
THROUGH THIS, THIS IS YOUR LIFE,
THIS IS YOUR FAMILY.
>> YEAH.
THEY'VE BEEN THE MOST AMAZING
SUPPORT SYSTEM.
I AM SO GRATEFUL FOR THEM, JUST
TO HAVE THEM.
[APPLAUSE]
[SIGHS]
>> BARBARA, HOW TOUGH IS THIS TO
WATCH HER SON GO THROUGH?
>> TOUGH.
YOU KNOW, THEY SAY THAT, AND
IT'S SO TRUE, THAT WHEN
SOMETHING HAPPENS, YOU WANT IT
TO HAPPEN TO YOU, BECAUSE WHEN
IT HAPPENS TO YOUR CHILD, IT IS
TWICE OR A TRIPLE, IT IS SO MUCH
HARDER FOR YOU TO TAKE IT, AND I
KNOW, I KNOW, I KNOW -- I KNOW
HOW HE FELT.
IT HASN'T BEEN EASY.
>> I KNOW HE HAS AN AMAZING
FAMILY TO FALL BACK ON.
I WANT TO TALK MORE TO YOU GUYS,
AND OBVIOUSLY WE HAVE A LOT TO
GET TO, SO STICK AROUND.
BE BACK WITH PETER.
AND COMING UP A LITTLE WHILE
LATER, HANNAH WILL COME OUT AND
JOIN US AS WELL.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
♪
[APPLAUSE]
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> WELCOME BACK, WE ARE LIVE
WITH OUR STUDIO AUDIENCE HERE IN
LOS ANGELES.
AND HERE'S PETER, WHO WAS JUST
SENT HOME IN AN EMOTIONAL ROSE
CEREMONY IN GREECE.
YOU JUST WATCHED IT FOR THE
FIRST TIME.
I WANT TO GO BACK BECAUSE YOU
HAD REALLY A GREAT CONNECTION
WITH HANNAH.
WHEN WAS IT THAT YOU FELT LIKE
THERE IS REALLY SOMETHING THERE,
THIS COULD BE REAL?
>> IT SO IT TOOK ME A WHILE TO
KIND OF EXPRESS TO HER HOW I FE,
BUT TO BE COMPLETELY HONEST, I
KNEW I WAS IN LOVE WITH HER WHEN
THE FIREWORKS WERE GOING ALL
OFTEN MOCKED VIA.
AND I REALLY HAVEN'T TOLD ANYONE
THAT, BUT THAT WAS THE FIRST
MOMENT WHERE I TRULY REALIZE
THAT, AND I HAD THE MOST AMAZING
DAY WITH HER.
I SAW ALL THE POTENTIAL IN THE
WORLD FOR ALL OF US.
>> DIETS PRETTY EARLY ON.
>> IT WAS.
>> YOUR HOMETOWN DATE, WE SAW
YOUR FAMILY, SUCH A STRONG
CONNECTION, YOU ARE CLEARLY IN
LOVE WITH HER BUT YOU COULDN'T
PULL THE TRIGGER.
WHAT MADE YOU HESITANT?
>> I JUST -- FROM THE BEGINNING,
HANNAH, SHE WAS PUSHING ME TO
OPEN UP AND BE AS VULNERABLE AS
I COULD, AND I TRIED MY HARDEST,
AND I DON'T KNOW.
FOR ME KNOWING THAT THERE WAS A
COUPLE GUYS LEFT, EVEN WHEN I
FINALLY TOLD HER, THERE WAS
THREE OTHER GUYS THERE, IT WAS
TOUGH FOR ME TO FINALLY OPEN UP
MYSELF COMPLETELY TO HER IN THAT
WAY, KNOWING THERE WAS STILL A
POSSIBILITY I WASN'T GOING TO BE
THE FINAL GUY.
SO I THINK THAT'S WHERE MY
HESITATION CAME FROM FINALLY
JUST OPENING UP AND TELLING HER.
>> WELL, IF IT'S ANY
CONSOLATION, I THINK SHE KNEW.
I THINK WE COULD ALL TELL.
>> I THINK SO TOO.
>> WHAT ARE YOUR FEELINGS NOW?
DO YOU STILL LOVE HER?
>> UM, I DON'T THINK YOU CAN
COMPLETELY FALL OUT OF LOVE WITH
SOMEONE WITHIN TWO MONTHS.
I'VE BEEN MOVING ON AND, YOU
KNOW, DOING MY BEST AT THAT, AND
I KNOW TIME WILL HEAL ALL
WOUNDS.
LIKE I SAID, A LITTLE PIECE OF
MY HEART WILL ALWAYS LOVE HER.
>> I KNOW IT'S BEEN TOUGH TO
WATCH THIS FOR THE FIRST TIME.
I CAN SEE THE EMOTION IN YOUR
FACE.
YOU KNOW HANNAH IS HERE.
SHE'S ABOUT TO COME OUT.
YOU'RE ABOUT TO SEE HER FOR THE
FIRST TIME.
>> [SIGHS]
AT YEAH.
I'VE BEEN THINKING ABOUT THIS
DAY FOR A WHILE.
BUT IT'LL BE GOOD.
IT'LL BE GOOD TO SEE HER.
>> WHAT IS THAT EMOTION GOING
THROUGH YOUR HEAD?
>> I JUST -- I'VE -- I'VE BEEN
DOING REALLY WELL ON MY OWN
TRYING TO FIND CLOSURE WITH ALL
THIS AND PUT IT BEHIND ME, TAKE
ALL THE GOOD THINGS WITH ME
MOVING FORWARD, BUT I JUST HAVE
BEEN LOOKING FORWARD TO THIS
CHANCE TO SEE HER FACE TO FACE
ONE MORE TIME AND KIND OF END
THIS CHAPTER IN THE RIGHT WAY.
>> WELL, WE ARE GOING TO DO
THIS.
PETER WILL COME FACE-TO-FACE
WITH HANNAH FOR THE FIRST TIME
SINCE THEY BROKE UP IN GREECE
WHEN WE COME BACK.
[APPLAUSE]
♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> WELCOME BACK TO THE LIVE,
DRAMATIC SEASON FINALE OF
"THE BACHELORETTE."
I AM HERE WITH PETER WHO HAS NOT
SEEN HANNAH SINCE HE LEFT
GREECE.
ARE YOU READY?
>> IT LET'S DO IT, YET.
>> ALL RIGHT.
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, HANNAH.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> HEY.
>> HAVE A SEAT.
WELCOME.
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU.
I KNOW THIS IS DIFFICULT, AS IT
IS FOR PETER.
YOU GUYS HAVEN'T SEEN EACH OTHER
SINCE THAT DATE IN GREECE, AND
IT HAS BEEN AN EMOTIONAL NIGHT
ALREADY, SO I'M JUST GOING TO
HAND IT OVER TO YOU, PETER, AND
THAT YOU TALK TO HANNAH.
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU.
WOW.
CAN'T BELIEVE THIS IS HAPPENING.
UM...
I GUESS STARTING FROM THE
NETHERLANDS AND MOVING FORWARD
TO HOMETOWNS AND HAVING THAT
GOES SO UNBELIEVABLY WELL WITH
MY FAMILY AND EVERYONE --
>> HEY, JACK.
>> JUST HAVING THAT GOES SO
WELL, THEN GOING INTO CRETE AND,
FROM MY PERSPECTIVE, HAVING THE
BEST TIME EVER, THEN THAT
GETTING BETTER AND BETTER, THAN
THE FANTASY SUITE AND RAKING UP
THE NEXT MORNING, FOR ME, THE
LAST TWO MONTHS, I'VE BEEN
TRYING TO PINPOINT WHAT IT WAS
THAT WAS THE TURNING POINT FOR
YOU OR THE POINT WHERE YOU
REALIZED IT WASN'T US AND YOU
MAY NOT HAVE AN ANSWER.
I WAS CURIOUS ABOUT THAT.
>> THERE WASN'T ANYTHING WRONG.
AND I KNOW THAT'S PROBABLY HARD
TO HEAR BECAUSE I WISH I COULD
GIVE YOU A CLEAR CONCRETE AN
ANSWER, BUT I TRULY THOUGHT YOU
WOULD MEET MY FAMILY, EVEN THAT
WHOLE WEEK, THAT LAST WEEK
TOGETHER, THE DATE AND THE
FANTASY SUITE DAY THAT WE HAD, I
THOUGHT --
>> I REMEMBER LEAVING.
>> YEAH.
>> AND I WAS SO SURE IT WAS US.
>> AND I REALLY THOUGHT YOU
WOULD MEET THEM.
BUT I DON'T KNOW.
I WAS FALLING IN LOVE WITH YOU,
BUT I ALSO WAS FALLING FOR TWO
OTHER GUYS TOO.
AND I WOKE UP THAT MORNING,
HONESTLY, IT WAS THAT MORNING,
AND HAD TO FOLLOW MY HEART.
>> YEAH.
>> IT WAS REALLY HARD FOR ME
TOO.
>> I KNOW.
AND THAT'S ALL I COULD HAVE
ASKED OF YOU.
AND YOU ARE LIKE THAT FROM NIGHT
ONE.
SO OBVIOUSLY I WISH IT WAS A
DIFFERENT RESULT IN THAT MOMENT
BUT, YOU KNOW, I RESPECT THAT.
>> I THINK MAYBE I WISH I WOULD
HAVE KNOWN A LITTLE BIT SOONER
ABOUT HOW YOU FELT AND HE WOULD
HAVE TOLD ME MAYBE, BECAUSE
I'M SCARED.
I WAS SCARED.
AND I THINK I FELT LIKE YOU WERE
SCARED TO LOVE ME, IF I COULD
THINK OF ANYTHING, AND THAT YOU
WERE APPREHENSIVE ABOUT SHARING
YOUR FEELINGS, AND, IF ANYTHING,
I WISH I WOULD HAVE KNOWN A
LITTLE BIT SOONER HOW YOU FELT.
BUT I FELT AGE.
>> YEAH
NO, THAT'S FAIR.
THAT'S TOTALLY FAIR.
I HAD ONE MORE QUESTION.
JUST, I'VE KIND OF HEARD OR SEEN
JUST WATCHING THIS BACK, YOU
REFER TO OUR RELATIONSHIP AS A
SLOW BURN.
AND JUST BEING COMPLETELY
HONEST, I WAS CURIOUS WHY YOU --
I DIDN'T UNDERSTAND, I GUESS,
WHERE THAT WAS COMING FROM.
>> YEAH, WELL, I MEAN, IT WAS
VERY PASSIONATE.
>> YEAH.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> BUT --
STOP.
[LAUGHTER]
FROM THE START, I ALWAYS ENJOYED
OUR TIME TOGETHER, BUT I DON'T
KNOW IF IT WAS JUST YOU NOT
EXACTLY EXPRESSING TO ME
VERBALLY HOW YOU FELT, IF THAT
HELD ME BACK FROM EMOTIONALLY
JUMPING THE GUN AND, LIKE, GOING
ALL IN.
EVERY TIME YOU WERE THERE, I
FELT LIKE WE WERE MOVING
FORWARD, AND I THINK THAT'S WHAT
HE MEANT BY THE SLOW BURN.
IT KEPT PROGRESSING.
BUT I THINK IT JUST WAS
CONTINUALLY PROGRESSING, AND
JUST WASN'T -- I THINK I NEEDED
TO HEAR THAT.
>> YEAH.
LIKE, YEAH.
>> UNDERSTAND, I'VE BEEN HURT
TOO, AND I KNOW IT'S HARD AND
IT'S SCARY TO SAY THAT, AND I
UNDERSTOOD IT ALL.
IT'S JUST, I HAD TO GO WITH WHAT
I FELT IN THAT MOMENT WAS THE
BEST FOR ME.
>> I CAN COMPLETELY UNDERSTAND
THAT.
THANK YOU FOR THAT.
>> I KNOW YOU PRETTY WELL BY
NOW.
>> YEAH.
>> THAT GOODBYE IT WAS EASILY
THE TOUGHEST.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> WHAT MADE IT SO DIFFICULT?
>> UM...
I DID -- I KNEW I WAS GOING TO
HURT YOU, BUT I WAS ALSO GETTING
HURT TOO BECAUSE I WAS FALLING
IN LOVE WITH YOU, AND THAT
DIDN'T JUST GO AWAY WHEN I SAID
GOODBYE.
IT'S BEEN REALLY HARD FOR ME TO
WATCH EVERYTHING AND TO WATCH
HOW UPSET I WAS THAT DAY BECAUSE
EVERYTHING THAT WE HAD WAS REAL,
AND THE WAY I FELT WAS REAL, AND
I KNOW THE WAY YOU FELT FOR ME
IT WAS REAL.
IT'S SO HARD BEING IN THIS
POSITION BECAUSE YOU DON'T KNOW
IF YOU ARE MAKING THE RIGHT
DECISION, AND I THINK I WAS
SCARED I WAS LETTING GO OF THE
PERFECT GUY.
>> YOU DID!
[LAUGHTER]
[APPLAUSE]
>> I DON'T KNOW IF YOU GUYS JUST
HEARD THAT.
SOMEONE JUST YELLED "YOU DID."
WOULD YOU HAVE CHANGED ANYTHING
LOOKING BACK?
>> HONESTLY, NO.
HANNAH, I UNDERSTAND WHERE
YOU'RE COMING FROM, AND I
TOTALLY GET THAT.
YOU HAVE A BUNCH OF OTHER GUYS,
IT'S NOT JUST ME IN THIS PROCESS
THAT YOU ARE TRYING TO FIGURE
OUT ALL THESE FEELINGS.
IT HAS TO BE SO INCREDIBLY TOUGH
FOR YOU.
BUT FOR ME, THIS ENTIRE JOURNEY,
I MADE IT A POINT TO ALWAYS BE
MYSELF.
I WASN'T GOING TO CHANGE MYSELF
FOR ANYONE ELSE.
I WASN'T GOING TO BE SOMEONE I
WASN'T, AND I WAS GOING TO IT --
[APPLAUSE]
I WASN'T GOING TO FORCE
ANYTHING.
I WAS GOING TO -- I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU HEARD BACK STAGE, BUT
OBVIOUSLY I FELT IT A LOT SOONER
THAN WHEN I TOLD YOU.
BUT I JUST WAS WAITING FOR THE
RIGHT MOMENT.
I DIDN'T WANT TO FORCE ANYTHING,
I WANTED IT TO BE GENUINE AND
ORGANIC.
SO I DON'T REGRET -- I TRULY
DON'T REGRET ANYTHING.
>> ON A LIGHTER NOTE, BECAUSE OF
YOU TWO, NOBODY WILL EVER LOOK
AT A WINDMILL THE SAME.
[LAUGHTER]
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> ALL RIGHT.
I MEAN, SINCE -- OH.
I MEAN, I WILL SAY, I, UM, I WAS
A LITTLE DISHONEST ABOUT
SOMETHING.
>> WHAT'S THAT?
>> NO, I MEAN, SINCE IT'S OUT
THERE, AND I DID SAY THERE IS
SOMETHING PETER AND I DID TWICE,
IT WAS ACTUALLY FOUR TIMES.
[LAUGHTER]
[APPLAUSE]
>> THE TRUTH IS OUT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU SAID THAT.
OH, MY GOD.
>> HUGHES A REALLY, REALLY SWEET
GUY.
>> BY THE WAY, PETER'S MOM IS
RIGHT THERE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
THIS IS SO WEIRD.
OH, MY GOD.
>> HE IS A GREAT CATCH.
>> PETER'S DAD, HIS CHEST JUST
PUFFED UP.
"THAT'S MY BOY."
SOMEWHERE, LUKE P.'S HEAD JUST
EXPLODED.
>> I WILL SAY, I STILL CAN
CONFIDENTLY SAY THAT JESUS STILL
LOVES BOTH OF US.
>> PETER, HANNAH, YOU GUYS GIVE
IT UP FOR PETER AND HANNAH.
WILL HANNAH HAVE HER HAPPY
ENDING?
OR MAYBE NOT.
WE'LL FIND OUT.
HANNAH WILL ALSO BE BACK WITH ME
LATER ON RIGHT HERE ON STAGE TO
TELL US ALL ABOUT THE LIVE
FINALE TOMORROW NIGHT.
SO STICK AROUND.
♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> WELCOME BACK TO OUR LIVE
2-NIGHT FINALE.
HANNAH IS DOWN TO HER FINAL TWO
MEN, TYLER AND JED.
AND SHE IS READY TO INTRODUCE
THEM TO HER FAMILY IN CRETE.
HOW WILL THESE NEXT TWO DAYS
AFFECT HANNAH'S FUTURE?
IT MIGHT NOT BE WHAT YOU THINK.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
♪
>> WE'RE HERE IN CRETE, GREECE.
IT'S SO SURREAL, SO MAGICAL.
I COULD NOT THINK OF A MORE
BEAUTIFUL PLACE TO GET ENGAGED,
AND I'M SO EXCITED.
♪
I HAVE TWO GUYS LEFT, JED AND
TYLER, AND I HAVE BEEN FALLING
IN LOVE WITH BOTH TYLER AND JED.
JED HAS BEEN SUCH A STABLE GUY
IN ALL OF THIS FOR ME.
I FEEL LIKE JED IS LIKE THAT
FOREVER, LIKE, BEST FRIEND OF A
PARTNER THAT I WANT.
AND TYLER IS SO SUPPORTIVE.
IT IS SEXY AND IT SHOWS, LIKE,
THAT HE IS A CONFIDENT MAN.
TODAY MY PARENTS ARE HERE IN
CRETE, AND I'M SO EXCITED.
BOTH OF THEM ARE GOING TO BE SO
WELCOMED BY MY FAMILY.
>> I'M VERY EXCITED TO SEE HER.
>> YOU'RE EXCITED TO SEE HER
BECAUSE YOU WANT TO KNOW SHE'S
OKAY?
>> MM-HMM.
>> YOU MISS HER?
>> DON'T MAKE ME CRY, SISSY.
>> I'M NOT --
>> DON'T CRY.
>> HEY!
OH.
MY FAMILY IS MEETING TYLER
TODAY.
HEY!
TYLER IS GOING TO MEET MY DAD,
ROBERT, AND MY MOM, SUSANNE.
AND I CANNOT WAIT FOR THEM TO
SEE WHAT AN AMAZING GUY HE IS.
IT'S GOING TO BE SO FUN.
WE'RE IN GREECE.
>> IT'S AWESOME.
>> IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
>> IT'S GORGEOUS.
>> SO I'M SO EXCITED FOR Y'ALL
TO MEET TYLER AND JED.
>> AND WE'RE GOING TO MEET TYLER
TODAY?
>> YOU'RE MEETING TYLER TODAY,
YEAH.
HIS PARENTS ARE DIVORCED, AND
HIS DAD HAS BEEN RECENTLY REALLY
SICK, AND HE HAS BEEN THE GLUE
FOR HIS FAMILY.
AND HE LOVES ME.
LIKE, HE HAS SAID HE LOVES ME.
BUT, LIKE, HONESTLY I WAS REALLY
WORRIED ABOUT LAST WEEK WITH
HIM, FANTASY SUITE, BECAUSE OUR
RELATIONSHIP'S BEEN REALLY
PHYSICAL.
I DIDN'T KNOW IF IT WAS I WAS
FALLING IN LUST WITH HIM OR
FALLING IN -- HAVE BEEN FALLING
IN LOVE WITH HIM.
LIKE, I DIDN'T KNOW.
>> RIGHT.
>> AND HE ACTUALLY BROUGHT IT UP
FIRST.
HE WAS LIKE, "I JUST WANT YOU TO
KNOW THERE'S SO MUCH MORE FOR ME
THAN THAT."
HE JUST WAS LIKE, "THERE'S A
TIME FOR THAT.
I JUST WANT TO BE WITH YOU."
AND I THINK THAT WAS THE MOMENT
I KNEW, LIKE, I HAVE BEEN
FALLING IN LOVE WITH HIM BUT
WOULDN'T ALLOW MYSELF TO BE
VULNERABLE IN THAT WAY.
SO I'M GOING TO GO GET HIM,
AND -- CAN'T WAIT FOR Y'ALL TO
ACTUALLY MEET HIM.
>> OKAY.
>> LET'S DO IT.
>> OKAY, GREAT, I'LL BE BACK.
>> OKAY.
>> LAST WEEK, I KNEW I HAD
FEELINGS FOR TYLER, BUT I DIDN'T
KNOW, HAVE I JUST BEEN FALLING
IN LUST THIS WHOLE TIME WITH
TYLER?
AND I FEEL LIKE I FINALLY HAVE
CLARITY, LIKE -- AND I HAVEN'T
SAID IT, BUT, LIKE, I HAVE BEEN
FALLING IN LOVE WITH TYLER.
>> SO EXCITED TO SEE YOU.
OOH.
HEY.
I THINK THAT'S WHY I WAS SO
EMOTIONAL, LIKE, HIM LEAVING OUR
OVERNIGHT, BECAUSE IT WAS LIKE,
OH, MY GOD.
I GET IT.
AND I WANT MY FAMILY TO SEE THAT
TODAY.
>> HEY.
HEY.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
>> THIS IS TYLER, Y'ALL.
>> HI, NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> HOW ARE YOU?
>> GOOD TO MEET THE BROWNS
TODAY.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> IT'S AN HONOR TO MEET THE
IN-LAWS.
THEY ARE GOING TO BE TOUGH ON ME
BECAUSE THEY'RE GOING TO SEE IF
I BEND OR BREAK, YOU KNOW.
AND I'M READY FOR IT.
>> SO, HEY.
ARE YOU NERVOUS MEETING US?
>> NO, I WAS EXCITED.
YOU GUYS SHOULD BE SO PROUD OF
THIS GIRL, THE WAY SHE'S
CONDUCTED HERSELF.
AND SHE'S JUST BEEN ABSOLUTELY
AMAZING AND SO MUCH FUN TO GET
TO KNOW.
WE'VE HAD THE BEST TIME.
>> HE'S A DANCER.
>> I LOVE TO DANCE.
>> NO, HE TOOK DANCE CLASSES,
LIKE, BALLET.
[LAUGHTER]
>> WELL, SO --
>> I WANT TO HEAR ABOUT THAT.
>> MY FIRST SEMESTER IN COLLEGE
WAS A ROUGH ONE.
I, LIKE, GOT KICKED OUT OF MY
ENGLISH CLASS.
I GOT, LIKE -- I GOT A D IN
ECON.
AND SO THEY MADE ME STAY ALL
SUMMER, AND THEY JUST THREW ME
IN ALL THESE CLASSES TO GET MY
GPA UP, AND THEN THEY THREW ME
IN, LIKE, A BUNCH OF DANCE
CLASSES.
>> THEY'RE HARD.
>> I WAS LIKE, WOW.
THIS IS SO MUCH FUN.
AND I JUST STUCK WITH IT.
I WAS ALMOST A DANCE MINOR BY
THE END OF IT.
>> HE SHOWED ME HIS PIROUETTE
AND I WAS LIKE, OH, HEY.
>> AND DID YOU SHOW HIM YOURS?
>> NO, I --
>> OH, YOU HAVEN'T -- YOU HAVE A
PIROUETTE?
NO, YOU HAVEN'T SHOWN ME.
>> NO, I'M NOT DOING THAT RIGHT
NOW.
>> TYLER AND HANNAH SEEM VERY
HAPPY WITH EACH OTHER RIGHT NOW,
AND SHE SEEMED TO LITERALLY
GLOW.
I DEFINITELY WANT THAT FOR HER
IN A RELATIONSHIP AND THAT HE
HELPS HER GROW AND THAT SHE
HELPS HIM GROW.
>> SO TELL ME HOW THIS
EXPERIENCE HAS BEEN FOR YOU.
>> THIS EXPERIENCE HAS BEEN --
IT'S BEEN WILD.
IT'S -- AT FIRST, I WAS LIKE,
WHAT HAVE I GOTTEN MYSELF INTO?
BUT, THE -- YOU KNOW, THE
RELATIONSHIP I'VE BUILT WITH
YOUR DAUGHTER HAS REALLY MADE
EVERYTHING WORTH IT.
>> HAVE YOU GUYS, LIKE, ARGUED
OR HAD DISAGREEMENTS AT ALL?
>> WE HAVEN'T REALLY HAD TOO
MUCH DISAGREEMENTS, BUT WE'VE
HAD, YOU KNOW, TIMES, LIKE --
WE'VE HAD VERY TOUGH TALKS.
>> I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU A
SCENARIO.
SO SAY YOU DO SOMETHING THAT SHE
DISAGREES WITH AND YOU KNOW
SHE'S NOT GOING TO LIKE IT.
ARE YOU GOING TO COME TO HER AND
TELL HER AND STRAIGHT UP BE
HONEST WITH HER?
>> OF COURSE.
>> OR ARE YOU GOING TO TRY TO
HIDE IT?
>> NO, THERE IS NO HIDING
THINGS.
I'M AN OPEN BOOK, AND I'M NOT
GOING TO HOLD BACK FROM HER.
I'M NOT GOING TO GO BEHIND HER
BACK EVER.
YOU KNOW, LIKE, MY PARENTS ARE
DIVORCED.
LIKE, I'VE SEEN WHAT GETS A
COUPLE TO THAT SITUATION.
>> IN OUR FAMILY, IT'S A
ONE-AND-DONE.
>> YEAH.
THAT'S HOW I WANT IT TO BE.
>> SO YOU'VE GOT TO BE, YOU
KNOW, WILLING TO WORK THROUGH
IT.
>> STICK IT OUT THROUGH ALL OF
I HAVE YOUR DAUGHTER'S BEST
INTERESTS, AND I REALLY DO LOVE
YOUR DAUGHTER.
AND I CAN STAND HERE AND SAY IT
AND BE 100% BEHIND IT, OR ELSE,
YOU KNOW, I WOULDN'T.
AND I WANT HER TO BE MY WIFE AND
I WANT TO BE HER BEST FRIEND AND
I WANT TO BE HER BIGGEST
CHEERLEADER.
>> IT SEEMS LIKE YOU KNOW WHERE
YOUR HEART IS.
TYLER KIND OF JUST BLEW ME AWAY
TODAY.
I THINK HE SO COMPLETELY LOVES
HER, LIKE, WITHOUT A DOUBT.
SEEMS VERY PROTECTIVE.
HE WAS PRETTY AMAZING ALL THE
WAY AROUND.
>> SHE SHARED WITH US A LITTLE
BIT ABOUT THE FANTASY SUITE.
AND WHAT WAS YOUR TAKE ON THAT?
>> UM, I HAVE SO MUCH RESPECT
FOR YOUR DAUGHTER AND WANT HER
TO FEEL LOVED AND CARED THE
RIGHT WAY, YOU KNOW.
BUT THE FANTASY SUITE, YOU KNOW,
WE JUST CONNECTED.
THERE WAS A LOT OF JUST TALK,
AND THAT'S KIND OF WHAT THAT
NIGHT WAS ALL ABOUT.
>> WELL, I RESPECT THAT, AND
THAT, YOU KNOW, SHOWS GOOD
CHARACTER BY BEING ABLE TO TAKE
THAT AND TURN IT INTO SOMETHING
THAT SHOULD BE MORE BEAUTIFUL
THAN JUST AN ACTION.
>> EXACTLY.
THERE'S A TIME AND PLACE FOR
EVERYTHING AND THAT WASN'T IT.
BEFORE I GOT OUT HERE, MY DAD
GOT REALLY SICK AND PUT A LOT OF
THINGS IN PERSPECTIVE FOR ME.
I LOVE YOUR DAUGHTER.
I WANT THAT GIRL TO BE THE
MOTHER OF MY KIDS.
YOU KNOW, I WANT HER TO LEAD MY
FAMILY IN FAITH THE WAY SHE'S
DONE SO FAR IN THIS TRIP AND TO
BE THAT STRONG WOMAN THAT SHE
IS.
I DON'T HAVE ANY SECOND-GUESSING
OR ANY DOUBT ABOUT ME AND HER AT
ALL.
>> TYLER SEEMS TO BE THE REAL
DEAL.
HE WAS HONEST, VERY SINCERE, AND
WILLING TO STEP UP AND TAKE CARE
OF HER THE WAY THAT I SEE FIT.
HE SEEMS TO BE VERY LOVING.
>> SO YOU TALKED WITH TYLER,
RIGHT?
>> I DID TALK TO TYLER.
>> HOW'D IT GO?
>> IT WENT REAL WELL, BECAUSE SO
MANY TIMES WHEN YOU GET TO THE
FANTASY SUITE, IT'S JUST ALL
ABOUT THE HOOKING UP.
>> AND YOU TALKED TO HIM ABOUT
THAT?
>> OF COURSE I DID.
WE DISCUSSED THAT, AND I TOLD
HIM THAT I WAS -- YOU KNOW, IT
MEANT A LOT TO ME THAT HE
HANDLED THAT SITUATION LIKE HE
DID, AND I RESPECTED HIM FOR NOT
WANTING IT JUST TO BE THAT
MOMENT.
>> AND THAT WAS WHEN IT CLICKED
FOR ME.
IT WAS LIKE, HE RESPECTS ME.
I THINK THAT WAS THE WHOLE
THING.
LIKE, HE RESPECTS ME SO MUCH.
>> I THINK HE HAS GOOD
INTENTIONS.
I MEAN, ANYBODY THAT'LL RESPECT
YOU LIKE HE DID, THEY GET A
KUDO.
>> I KNOW.
I KNOW MY DAD REALLY LIKED TYLER
AND WAS REALLY PROUD THAT I HAD
SOMEONE SO GREAT LIKE TYLER THAT
LOVED ME.
SO...
>> WHAT DID I THINK?
>> YEAH.
>> I MEAN, SO FAR I FEEL REALLY
GOOD.
AND I LOVE THE FACT THAT HE
MAKES YOU HAPPY AND THAT HE WILL
DANCE WITH YOU.
LIKE, THERE'S SO MUCH ABOUT HIM
I LIKE.
>> MM-HMM.
>> DO YOU SEE YOURSELF GETTING
ENGAGED TO HIM AT THE END?
>> YEAH.
I FEEL REALLY GOOD ABOUT THE
DAY, AND I COULD TOTALLY SEE
TYLER BEING A PART OF MY FAMILY.
>> HAVE A GOOD ONE.
>> BYE.
>> I FEEL LIKE HE CONTINUES TO
SHOW ME MORE AND MORE OF WHO HE
IS.
I REALIZE THAT ALL THE HOLDS
THAT I'VE PUT ON MY FEELINGS
TOWARDS HIM, THAT THE FEELINGS
THAT I HAD WERE ALWAYS REAL.
I WANTED TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT
SOMETHING.
UM, YOU'VE BEEN SO VULNERABLE
AND HONEST WITH ME THE WHOLE
TIME ABOUT HOW YOU'RE FEELING
AND WHERE YOU ARE, AND I FEEL
LIKE I HAVEN'T BEEN AS MUCH WITH
YOU TO THIS POINT, BUT I THINK I
HAD TO FIGURE IT OUT A LITTLE
BIT.
AND I THINK I WAS WORRYING IF I
WAS -- WHAT OUR RELATIONSHIP WAS
AND WHAT IT WAS FOR ME AND IN MY
HEART AND DIDN'T KNOW IF IT WAS
I WAS LUSTING OVER YOU IN A WAY
AND, LIKE, WHAT WE HAD AND JUST
WANTED IT BE THAT AND IF I WAS
JUST FALLING IN LUST WITH YOU
THIS WHOLE TIME.
BUT I KNOW THAT I'VE BEEN
FALLING IN LOVE WITH YOU.
I'VE BEEN EXCITED TO TELL YOU
THAT.
>> IT MEANS THE WORLD TO ME.
I'M SO HAPPY TO HEAR THAT.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
TYLER HAS A PIECE OF MY HEART
AND, LIKE, I DON'T KNOW.
I'M JUST SO EXCITED.
I NEVER THOUGHT I'D BE THIS
EXCITED ABOUT TYLER.
>> THANK YOU FOR TODAY.
>> THANK YOU.
>> I HOPE IT GAVE YOU CLARITY
AND I HOPE IT WAS EVERYTHING YOU
NEEDED.
>> IT WAS.
>> I LOVE YOU.
GO HAVE FUN WITH YOUR FAMILY,
ALL RIGHT?
>> I WILL.
>> I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
GO HAVE FUN.
ENJOY IT.
CHERISH THEM.
I'LL SEE YOU SOON.
>> OKAY.
THANK YOU.
BEST DAY.
>> I LOVE YOU.
>> MY FEELINGS FOR HIM, THEY
KIND OF SNUCK UP ON ME VERY
QUICKLY, AND I CAN DEFINITELY
SEE A FUTURE WITH TYLER.
I'M, LIKE -- I'M JUST SO
SURPRISED.
I -- THAT IS, LIKE, THE WORD.
LIKE, IF THEY'RE LIKE, "TYLER,"
I'D BE LIKE, "SURPRISE."
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> WOW, IT IS SAFE TO SAY,
HANNAH'S FAMILY LOVES TYLER AND
EVERYONE ELSE DOES TOO.
WHEN WE COME BACK, IT IS JED'S
TURN, WILL HE WIN THEM OVER?
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> SO HOW ARE YOU FEELING TODAY?
>> UM, I'M EXCITED FOR YOU TO
MEET JED.
>> WE'RE EXCITED.
>> BUT I'LL JUST GO AHEAD AND
SAY, I'M A LITTLE, LIKE, UH,
NERVOUS, I THINK.
>> WHY?
>> FOR US TO MEET HIM?
>> IT'S NOT BECAUSE I'M
CONCERNED ABOUT JED OR TYLER,
SO, TO HAVE, LIKE, TWO REALLY
GOOD GUYS, AND SO, IT'S, LIKE,
HITTING ME A LITTLE BIT.
>> YOU'RE GETTING NERVOUS YOU'RE
ABOUT TO HAVE TO MAKE A
DECISION.
>> MM-HMM.
>> SO I'M JUST FREAKING OUT.
BUT, UM, JED HAS BEEN THE ONE
FROM THE VERY BEGINNING THAT I
WAS JUST LIKE, THIS PERSON FITS
IN MY LIFE.
I'M REALLY EXCITED FOR Y'ALL TO
SEE WHAT I SEE.
SO I'M GOING TO GO GET HIM.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> OKAY.
PUMPED THAT MY FAMILY WAS ABOUT
TO MEET BOTH TYLER AND JED
BECAUSE I KNEW I HAD MADE THE
BEST DECISION.
IT WENT GREAT WITH TYLER
YESTERDAY, AND GOING INTO TODAY,
IT'S LIKE, I'M VERY ANXIOUS FOR
MY FAMILY TO MEET JED.
I WANT THEM TO SEE WHAT I SEE.
>> OOH-HOO, I LIKE THE BLUE.
>> HEY.
OOH!
[GIGGLES]
>> I'M REALLY -- I'M TRYING TO
GIVE HIM -- JED -- A FAIR SHOT,
BUT YESTERDAY, THE BAR WAS HIGH.
>> IT WAS HIGH.
>> IT WAS REALLY HIGH.
>> HELLO.
>> HI.
>> THIS IS JED.
>> I'M JED.
I'M A HUGGER.
>> HEY, JED.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> WE'RE HUGGERS.
>> TODAY IS REALLY IMPORTANT FOR
ME BECAUSE I WANT TO LET
HANNAH'S FAMILY KNOW HOW I FEEL
ABOUT HER, AND MOST IMPORTANTLY,
I JUST REALLY WANT THEM TO SEE
THAT I GENUINELY AND
WHOLEHEARTEDLY CARE ABOUT THEIR
DAUGHTER.
>> YOU CAN START.
ABOUT MEETING ME.
>> MEETING YOU.
OKAY, SO THE LIMO PULLS UP TO
THE MANSION, AND I WALKED UP TO
HER, AND I JUST TOLD HANNAH
THAT, YOU KNOW, IT'S VERY
EVIDENT THAT SHE SHINES ON THE
OUTSIDE BECAUSE SHE'S BEAUTIFUL,
BUT IT WAS ALSO GOING TO BE VERY
IMPORTANT, YOU KNOW, THAT I GET
TO SEE WHAT'S ON THE INSIDE.
>> THEN HE PLAYED ME A SONG THAT
HE WROTE, AND IT WAS REALLY
GOOD.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH
HANNAH'S FILLED YOU IN, BUT I'M
A MUSICIAN AND SONGWRITER, AND
THAT'S WHAT I'VE DEVOTED MY TIME
TO AND CHOSE.
THAT'S THE PATH THAT I'VE
CHOSEN.
THIS WEEK FOR ME IS JUST HUGE,
ESPECIALLY, LIKE, MEETING YOU
GUYS.
I'M VERY HONORED, AND I HAVE THE
BEST INTENTIONS, THE MOST PURE
INTENTIONS ON WATCHING AFTER HER
AND LOVING HER THROUGH
EVERYTHING.
>> SO IT'S BEEN REALLY GOOD.
I'M REALLY EXCITED.
>> JED, YOU KNOW, IS PLEASANT.
I LIKED THE WAY THEY LOOKED AT
EACH OTHER.
BUT ALSO YESTERDAY THERE WAS A
CONNECTION.
ALL I WANTED TO KNOW WITH MY
CONVERSATION THROUGH JED WAS HOW
HE WAS GOING TO PROVIDE FOR HER.
I WAS JUST CONCERNED THAT THERE
WAS A DIFFERENCE BETWEEN THE TWO
BOYS AND THAT SHE NEEDS TO MAKE
WHO IS GOING TO BE HER BEST
LIFE PARTNER.
HEY, JED.
YOU KNOW, I'M GLAD YOU
CAME OUT HERE TO HAVE A FEW
WORDS WITH ME.
I JUST WANT TO FIND OUT A FEW
THINGS.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> YOU KNOW, I NEED TO FIND OUT
WHAT YOUR GOALS ARE IN LIFE, YOU
KNOW, OTHER THAN WITH HANNAH,
BUT WHAT YOUR GOALS ARE.
>> RIGHT.
SO I GAVE UP A LOT OF OTHER
OPPORTUNITIES IN MY LIFE TO GO
AFTER MY DREAM, AND I MOVED TO
NASHVILLE FOR SONGWRITING, AND
I'M EXCITED FOR THAT.
AND --
>> ONE OF THE THINGS THAT I KNOW
THAT ARE GOING TO BE NECESSARY
IS PROVIDING FOR HANNAH, BECAUSE
SHE'S ALWAYS BEEN, YOU KNOW, OUR
MAIN PRIORITY, AND THAT WAS THE
REASON I WAS ASKING, YOU KNOW,
WHAT YOUR GOALS ARE AS FAR AS
FINANCIALLY BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, I
WANT TO KIND OF SEE -- YOU KNOW,
YOU ARE STILL YOUNG, BUT THERE
HAS TO BE A DIRECTION.
>> YOU KNOW, MY GOAL AS FAR AS
FINANCES AND STUFF GO IN THE
FUTURE, I JUST WANT TO HAVE AS
MANY FACETS OF INCOME AND BACKUP
PLANS AS I CAN SO THAT NOT ONLY
CAN I SUPPORT MYSELF BUT, YOU
KNOW, A FAMILY SOMEDAY.
AND, YOU KNOW, AT THIS POINT, MY
MOST MAJOR ACCOMPLISHMENT IS
THAT I SIGNED A DEAL WITH A
DOG FOOD COMPANY.
I'VE ALREADY WRITTEN, LIKE,
THEIR JINGLE.
AND THAT'S BEEN, LIKE, MY FIRST
REAL BREAKTHROUGH THAT I WAS
LIKE, OH, THIS IS THE START OF
SOMETHING.
>> YOU KNOW, I'M JUST TRYING TO
LOOK OUT FOR HER.
>> RIGHT.
>> BECAUSE THE NO RETURN POLICY
DOES HOLD UP.
I CONSIDER MARRIAGE AS A
ONE-TIME DEAL.
>> RIGHT.
>> YOU KNOW, SOMETIMES THE
FINANCIAL SITUATIONS ARE THE
PROBLEMS AND SOMETIMES IT'S THE
OTHER THINGS, BUT IT'S AMAZING
HOW MANY TIMES THAT IS THE MAIN
PROBLEM.
YOU KNOW, I'M A MAN THAT WORKS
14, 16 HOURS A DAY TO MAKE SURE
THEY ARE TAKEN CARE OF.
WE JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE THAT
IT'S THE RIGHT FIT...
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> BECAUSE IT'S ONE COHESIVE
FAMILY THAT WE TRY TO BUILD.
>> I FEEL A LITTLE CONFUSED.
I WAS PRAYING THAT THEY WOULD
SEE HOW WE WERE AROUND EACH
OTHER AND SEE HOW COMFORTABLE
AND NATURAL IT IS AND REAL.
>> Y'ALL HAVE GOT SOME BIG
DECISIONS AHEAD.
I MEAN, YOUR MUSIC CAREER -- I
KNOW IT'S HARD.
I DON'T HAVE TO TELL YOU THAT.
YOU'VE BEEN IN NASHVILLE FOR A
WHILE NOW, RIGHT?
I THINK?
>> IT SEEMED LIKE THEY WERE
MAINLY CONCERNED WITH, UM, THE
FINANCIAL ASPECT OF OUR
RELATIONSHIP.
>> HOPEFULLY YOU HIT IT BIG, AND
THEN THAT'S EVEN HARD.
>> YEAH.
THERE ARE A LOT OF CRAZY THINGS
THAT COME WITH MUSIC, BUT I SEE
AND I'M SURROUNDED BY PEOPLE
THAT DO RELATIONSHIPS THERE AND
WHO HAVE AMAZING, BEAUTIFUL, AND
SUCCESSFUL RELATIONSHIPS.
UM...
THEY DON'T THINK I'M ADEQUATE OR
SOMETHING.
BUT I KNOW HANNAH WILL DO THE
RIGHT THING FOR HER.
>> WELL, HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT
JED AND I TOGETHER?
>> UM, HE HAS QUALITIES, BUT
HE'S -- OBVIOUSLY, HE'S A
MUSICIAN.
HE IS IN NASHVILLE.
>> MM-HMM, MM-HMM.
>> HAVE YOU THOUGHT ABOUT, LIKE,
THE LIFESTYLE?
IT'S A LOT OF NIGHTS IN BARS FOR
RIGHT NOW, PLAYING ALL HOURS OF
THE NIGHT.
I MEAN...
[CLEARS THROAT]
AND ULTIMATELY THIS IS YOUR
DECISION.
>> NO, I WANT TO KNOW.
>> BUT TYLER JUST IS ON HIS OWN.
I DON'T KNOW, JUST --
>> I KNEW THIS WAS FRICKIN'
GOING TO HAPPEN.
>> WELL, I'M SORRY.
IT'S GOT TO -- YOU'VE GOT TO
THINK ABOUT THESE THINGS.
I MEAN, THIS IS IT.
AND SO I'M TELLING YOU WHAT I
SEE AS A MOM.
I LOVE YOU MORE THAN ANYTHING IN
THE WORLD.
YOU KNOW, YOU ARE JUST
EVERYTHING TO ME.
I WANT SOMEBODY THAT WOULD --
THAT WOULD LOVE YOU LIKE I KNOW
YOU SHOULD BE LOVED.
>> I KNOW.
I PROMISE I WILL.
I APPRECIATE MY PARENTS' OPINION
AND THEIR CONCERN AND THEIR LOVE
AND SUPPORT FOR ME, BUT THIS IS
NOT ABOUT ANYBODY ELSE BUT ME,
WHAT I FEEL IN MY HEART.
BUT NOW I'M FREAKING OUT.
♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> HOW DID IT GO WITH JED?
>> IT WENT WELL WITH JED.
YOU KNOW, WE HAD A GREAT
CONVERSATION.
BEAT AROUND THE BUSH A LITTLE
BIT, BUT I THINK THAT'S KIND OF
HIS PERSONALITY TO OVEREXPLAIN
THINGS WHEREAS THE OTHER ONE WAS
A LITTLE BIT MORE DIRECT ABOUT
THINGS.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> WELL...
YOU KNOW, STRETCHES THINGS OUT A
LITTLE BIT LONGER AND JUST NOT
DIRECT ANSWERS, YOU KNOW --
>> ABOUT WHAT?
>> WELL, THE NUMBER ONE THING
THAT I ASKED HIM IS, YOU KNOW,
AS FAR AS HIS PLANS IN THE
FUTURE, YOU KNOW, IF Y'ALL DID
MOVE FORWARDS ON THIS, YOU KNOW,
WHAT WAS HIS GOAL IN LIFE?
AND OF COURSE IT WAS THE MUSIC
INDUSTRY.
AND I ASKED HIM WHAT HIS
ACCOMPLISHMENTS WERE UP TO THIS
POINT, AND HE WAS VERY PROUD OF
THE DOG FOOD JINGLE THAT HE DID.
AND --
>> THAT'S NOT WHAT --
>> THAT'S WHAT HE SAID THAT HE
WAS, YOU KNOW, PROUD OF RIGHT
NOW.
>> YEAH.
>> ALL I'M DOING WAS REPEATING,
YOU KNOW, WHAT I TALKED ABOUT
WITH HIM.
YOU KNOW, YOU ARE MY NUMBER ONE
PRIORITY.
THAT'S THE REASON WE ARE HERE,
TO HELP YOU AND SUPPORT YOU, NOT
JUST, YOU KNOW, SAY EVERYTHING
IS OKAY AND COOL.
WE WANT TO BE HERE WITH YOU.
>> BUT, I MEAN -- I -- I OF
COURSE WANT TO BE -- MY HUSBAND
TO BE ABLE TO PROVIDE FOR ME,
BUT I ALSO KNOW THAT I'M GOING
TO BE ABLE TO -- I'M GOING TO BE
SUCCESSFUL AND I'M GOING TO BE
ABLE TO PROVIDE FOR MY FAMILY
TOO.
AND I KNOW I HAVE ALL THE
TALENTS AND GIFTS TO BE ABLE TO
GIVE MYSELF THE LIFE THAT I WANT
TOO.
>> BUT STILL THE MAN OF THE
HOUSE STILL HAS HIS OBLIGATIONS
TOO.
HE SHOULDN'T DEPEND ON THE
WOMAN -- I'M NOT SAYING HE
WOULD -- BUT AS THE MAN OF OUR
HOUSE, I NEED TO KNOW WHAT THE
MAN OF YOUR HOUSE IS GOING TO
DO.
>> OKAY.
I WANT TO GET PAST THAT.
I GET THAT.
AND ASK YOU ABOUT --
>> RIGHT, I DO TOO.
>> WHAT HE SAID ABOUT HOW HE
FELT ABOUT ME.
>> WELL, I WAS GOING TO GET TO
THAT.
>> OKAY.
>> YOU KNOW, BUT HE SAYS THAT HE
DOES LOVE YOU.
>> HE DOES.
I CAN TELL YOU HAVE CONCERNS, SO
JUST -- WILL YOU JUST SAY THEM?
WHAT YOU FEEL ABOUT HIM THEN?
BECAUSE I CAN JUST TELL, 'CAUSE
YOU'RE DOING THE, "WELL, THIS IS
WHAT HE SAID," WHICH, I KNOW
YOU'RE NOT TRYING TO BE
NEGATIVE, BUT IF YOU HAVE
NEGATIVE THOUGHTS, THEN JUST
TELL ME.
>> I'M TRYING TO BE SUPPORTIVE,
BECAUSE I DON'T WANT YOU TO
SETTLE FOR ANYTHING.
I WANT YOU TO MAKE SURE THAT YOU
MAKE THE RIGHT CHOICE, AND
THAT'S AS HONEST AS I CAN BE.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M -- I'M GOING TO GET UP FOR
JUST A SECOND, OKAY?
RIGHT NOW, I'M SO SCARED THAT
WITH WHOEVER I END UP AT THE END
THAT I WON'T COMPLETELY BE READY
TO LET GO OF THE OTHER PERSON.
I DON'T WANT TO BE, LIKE, AS
SOON AS I GET ENGAGED, BE LIKE,
"DID I MAKE THE RIGHT DECISION?"
I DON'T WANT TO FEEL LIKE THAT.
>> HEY.
>> I HAVE TWO REALLY STRONG
RELATIONSHIPS AND TWO REALLY
GREAT GUYS, BUT I DON'T WANT TO
NOT BE 100% SURE.
>> TALK TO ME, BABY.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
I DON'T KNOW -- I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO SAY.
>> NO MATTER WHAT, IT'S ALL
GOING TO BE ALL RIGHT.
I FEEL REALLY GOOD ABOUT US.
I HAVE FOR A LONG TIME.
>> I JUST, LIKE --
I DON'T THINK THAT --
I'M JUST --
I THINK -- I THINK IT'S OBVIOUS
THAT WE, LIKE, HAVE A GREAT TIME
TOGETHER AND -- I DON'T
WANT TO TALK ABOUT ANOTHER
PERSON, BUT -- LIKE, BECAUSE I
KNOW YOU DON'T WANT TO HEAR
THAT.
>> I DON'T CARE.
LIKE, TALK TO ME.
I DON'T CARE.
I LOVE YOU, AND I WANT TO KNOW
HOW YOU FEEL RIGHT NOW.
AND I DON'T GIVE A [BLEEP] ABOUT
ME RIGHT NOW.
>> [CLEARS THROAT]
WITH TYLER, THIS HAS BEEN
DEVELOPING FOR A WHILE, AND THEN
YESTERDAY WENT REALLY, REALLY
WELL.
AND HE WAS JUST VERY
STRAIGHTFORWARD ABOUT HOW HE
FELT ABOUT ME AND EVERYTHING,
AND I THINK -- I'M NOW CONFUSED.
[BLEEP] ME.
THIS IS WHY YOU DON'T DATE TWO
PEOPLE AT THE SAME TIME.
[SIGHS]
I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE, LIKE,
I'M REALLY, LIKE, SEEING A CLEAR
VISION OF, LIKE, EVERYTHING.
I DON'T KNOW.
♪
>> YOU KNOW I BELIEVE IN US.
YOU KNOW THAT -- YOU KNOW HOW I
FEEL ABOUT YOU.
BUT MORE THAN ANYTHING, HANNAH,
UM, YOU KNOW, LIKE -- YOU KNOW I
BELIEVE IN YOU.
>> I KNOW.
♪
>> BUT, BABY, WE KNOW WHAT WE
HAVE.
>> YEAH.
>> THAT'S -- I GUESS THAT'S WHAT
SCARES ME MORE THAN ANYTHING.
>> I JUST -- I'M GETTING REALLY
NERVOUS BECAUSE TWO PEOPLE ARE
IN MY HEART AT THE SAME TIME AND
I DON'T WANT TO MAKE THE WRONG
DECISION.
IT'S REALLY, REALLY HARD AND
BRINGS IN A LOT OF DOUBT AND
FEAR.
NOW I'M FREAKING OUT.
[APPLAUSE]
>> HOW IS HANNAH GOING TO FIGURE
THIS OUT?
MAYBE SHE WON'T.
WELL, SHE'S GOT ONE MORE DATE
EACH WITH JED AND TYLER, A LOT
OF PRESSURE NOT TO MAKE A
MISTAKE A.
HANNAH WILL BE BACK OUT ON STAGE
TO TALK ABOUT THAT LATER.
IF YOU REALLY WANT THE INSIDE
SCOOP FROM A COUPLE OF PEOPLE
WHO KNOW A LITTLE SOMETHING
ABOUT BEING THE BACHELORETTE,
MAKE SURE TO LISTEN INTO
"THE BACHELOR HAPPY HOUR," A
COUPLE OF FORMER BACHELORETTES,
THEY ARE HERE TONIGHT, ALI, GOOD
TO SEE YOU, GIRL, THEY HAVE GOT
AN EXCLUSIVE INTERVIEW WITH
PETER, AND I AM GUESSING THEY
HAVE AT LEAST FOUR QUESTIONS NOW
ABOUT A WINDMILL.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
♪
[GOATS BLEATING]
>> WAKING UP THIS MORNING, I'M
ANXIOUS.
MY MEET THE FAMILY WITH JED
DIDN'T GO SO WELL.
MY FAMILY HAD DOUBTS ABOUT HIM.
THESE NEXT TWO DATES ARE REALLY
IMPORTANT FOR ME TO GAIN CLARITY
IN KNOWING WHO I WANT TO BE WITH
IN THE END.
>> THERE SHE IS.
>> HEY.
>> HEY, GIRL.
>> HEY, BOY.
[LAUGHS]
TODAY IS A BIG DAY.
>> OH, MAN.
>> THIS IS MY LAST DATE WITH
TYLER TO FIND OUT IF I REALLY
CAN SEE HIM AS MY HUSBAND.
[SQUEALS]
HEY.
>> MY GIRL.
WOW.
>> HOW ARE YOU?
>> AMAZING.
>> WELL, WE HAVE A REALLY FUN
DAY TODAY.
THERE IS ONE CHALLENGE THAT I
STILL FEEL LIKE WE NEED TO
OVERCOME TOGETHER.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> OKAY, SO LET'S GO.
>> OH, GOD.
[LAUGHTER]
HOW ARE YOU?
>> I'M GREAT.
>> I MISSED YOU.
>> UM, I MISSED YOU.
BUT WE ARE GOING HORSEBACK
RIDING AGAIN.
>> ALL RIGHT, WE CAN TRY THIS
AGAIN, RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
I THINK YOU HAVE A LITTLE WORK
TO DO.
>> YES, I DO.
>> SO I THOUGHT WE WOULD --
>> REDEEM MYSELF.
>> WE WOULD DO A REDO.
>> ALL RIGHT, LET'S DO IT.
I'M NOT GOING TO LIVE, I AM
FREAKING OUT A LITTLE BIT.
I'M PRETTY FEARFUL OF HORSES,
AND THE LAST HORSEBACK RIDING
DATE IN THE HAGUE, YOU KNOW, THE
WHOLE TIME, I WAS FIGHTING FOR
MY HORSE JUST TO GET CLOSE TO
HANNAH, AND WE COULDN'T GET IT
RIGHT AT ALL AND COULDN'T FIGURE
IT OUT.
>> [LAUGHS]
>> COME HERE, BUDDY.
>> HEY, YOU HAVE TO BE
COMFORTABLE.
>> BUILDING THE BOND RIGHT NOW.
THAT'S WHAT I'M DOING.
ALL RIGHT, I'M GOING FOR IT.
>> OKAY, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
[LAUGHS]
>> MY HORSE IS ACTING WILD ONCE
AGAIN.
I'M LIKE, OH, GREAT, HERE WE GO.
NOW HE KNOWS I'M GETTING ON.
>> YOU GOT IT.
ALL RIGHT, I'M HERE.
COME HERE.
YOU CAN COME -- OH.
IT MIGHT BE ANOTHER ONE OF THESE
DATES.
>> WE GOT THIS.
THERE WE GO.
NOW WE'RE IN HERE TIGHT.
>> THIS IS GOOD.
>> WE GOT THIS.
NOW WE GOT THIS.
LOOK AT US.
>> WE'VE COME SO FAR.
>> WE HAVE.
LOOK AT US.
IT'S LIKE OUR RELATIONSHIP.
>> YEAH.
[LAUGHTER]
>> OH, WOW.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
♪
>> LAST TIME I SAW TYLER WAS
WITH MY FAMILY, AND IT WENT SO
GREAT.
>> LIKE, TODAY, I WAS LIKE A
GIDDY LITTLE KID GETTING READY.
>> I FEEL LIKE NOW THAT I'VE
BEEN ABLE TO ADMIT TO HIM THAT
IT IS LOVE, THAT I HAVE BEEN
FALLING IN LOVE WITH HIM, OUR
RELATIONSHIP IS SO MUCH MORE
COMFORTABLE AND FEELS RIGHT.
>> IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
>> IT'S HARD NOT TO ADMIRE HOW
BEAUTIFUL IT IS AND HOW FAR
WE'VE COME.
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
>> AMAZING.
WE LEFT YOUR PARENTS NOT TOO
LONG AGO.
>> I KNOW.
>> THAT WAS AN AMAZING DAY.
>> IT WAS REALLY GOOD.
>> YOUR DAD IS, LIKE, SUCH A
SWEET GUY.
AND --
>> YEAH.
>> I WANTED TO LET HIM KNOW,
LIKE, YOUR DAUGHTER WILL ALWAYS
BE PROTECTED.
SHE'LL ALWAYS BE SAFE.
YOU KNOW, SHE'S ALWAYS GOING TO
BE LOVED.
>> HE'S ON BOARD.
I MEAN, I COULD TELL HE WAS
COMFORTABLE BECAUSE WE COULD
STILL -- IT WASN'T, LIKE, THIS
SERIOUS, SERIOUS CONVERSATION.
HE TOLD ME EVERYTHING YOU SAID,
BUT I COULD JUST TELL HE WAS
CONFIDENT ABOUT HOW MOTIVATED
YOU ARE AND DRIVEN AND, YEAH.
I DIDN'T EVEN -- LIKE I HAD TO
DEFEND EVERYTHING.
THEY WERE REALLY HAPPY.
>> THAT'S AWESOME TO HEAR.
>> YEAH.
>> IF IT WASN'T FOR YOU PUSHING
ME, LIKE, I WOULDN'T BE ABLE TO
HAVE THOSE -- THAT GOOD OF TALKS
WITH YOUR FAMILY, YOU KNOW?
AND, LIKE, YOU'VE JUST PUSHED ME
TO SUCH A LEVEL THAT I'VE NEVER
BEEN TO, AND YOU, YOU KNOW,
TELLING ME THAT YOU WERE FALLING
IN LOVE WITH ME, I COULDN'T BE
HAPPIER WITH WHERE WE'RE AT.
AND, I MEAN, I'M WITH YOU, AND I
DON'T WANT TO BE ANYWHERE ELSE.
LIKE, THERE'S NOTHING I EVER
WANT MORE.
JUST TO LOOK AT YOU AND BE HERE
AND -- WHEREVER WE ARE THOUGH.
YOU KNOW, WE COULD BE IN A
LITTLE APARTMENT TRYING TO ARGUE
ABOUT WHAT THE PAINT WE'RE
PUTTING ON THE WALLS, YOU KNOW?
LIKE, I JUST WANT TO BE THERE,
YOU KNOW?
YOU KNOW, LIKE I SAID ON SPA
DAY, IF I COULD WAKE UP AND SEE
THESE EYES AND THOSE DIMPLES AND
THAT SMILE AND START MY DAY, I'D
BE THE LUCKIEST AND HAPPIEST GUY
IN THE WORLD.
♪
>> I'M SO HAPPY WITH TYLER.
AND I FEEL LIKE HE IS SO SWEET
AND SO KIND BUT FUNNY, AND I
LOVE THAT TYLER IS A GUY THAT
WILL MAKE SURE I'M TAKEN CARE OF
AND I KNOW I'LL BE TAKEN CARE
OF.
AND I THINK HE CAN SEE THAT WITH
THIS FAMILY.
I MEAN, HE LOVES ME AND CARES
ABOUT ME AND JUST WANTS TO DO
WHATEVER IS BEST FOR OUR
RELATIONSHIP.
IT'S CRAZY WE'RE HERE.
I CAN DEFINITELY SEE A FUTURE
WITH TYLER.
LIKE, TOTALLY.
♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> MY DATE WITH TYLER TODAY WAS
GREAT.
WE WERE JUST SO MUCH MORE IN
TUNE WITH EACH OTHER, AND HE WAS
JUST SO MUCH MORE CONFIDENT IN
OUR RELATIONSHIP.
WE JUST HAD TRULY ONE OF THE
BEST DATES TOGETHER.
>> HEY.
>> HEY!
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> MM.
>> WELCOME HOME.
WELCOME TO MY CRIB.
>> THANKS.
AFTER TONIGHT, THE NEXT TIME I
SEE HIM IS ON PROPOSAL DAY, AND
SO I JUST WANT TO LEAVE HERE
FEELING REALLY CONFIDENT ABOUT
WHERE WE ARE.
>> WELL, WE'RE HERE.
>> I KNOW.
THIS IS CRAZY.
TODAY WAS SO MUCH FUN.
>> IT WAS FUN.
>> DID YOU ENJOY YOURSELF?
>> I HAD THE BEST TIME.
>> WE CRUSHED THE HORSES.
>> I WAS REALLY PROUD OF YOU.
>> YEAH.
UNREAL.
SO MUCH FUN.
AND WE OVERCAME THAT OBSTACLE.
LIKE, WE CAN OVERCOME ANYTHING.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> LIKE, WE CAN OVERCOME
ANYTHING.
>> FEAR OF HORSES, YOU KNOW.
>> WE SURPASSED THAT, YOU KNOW.
JUST TOOK, YOU KNOW, YOU
CHIRPING ME FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
>> JUST A LITTLE.
>> AND MAKING FUN OF ME FOR A
COUPLE WEEKS.
YOU KNOW, BUT WE GOT IT
TOGETHER.
WE GOT IT TOGETHER.
>> IT WAS BEAUTIFUL TOO.
>> YEAH, OH, GORGEOUS.
SO MUCH FUN.
I LOVED OUR TALK.
AND IT WAS SO -- IT FELT AMAZING
TO HEAR, YOU KNOW, HOW YOUR
FAMILY RESPONDED TO ME AND THEN
TO HEAR WHAT YOU SAID.
AND IT WAS JUST A SPECIAL DAY.
AND NOW WE ARE HERE.
>> I KNOW.
SO, FOR REAL, LIKE, AFTER THE
DAY, LIKE, DID YOU FEEL GOOD
ABOUT IT BEFORE YOU TALKED TO
ME?
>> OH, I FELT AMAZING.
>> OKAY.
>> LIKE, RIGHT NOW, I'M
STARTING TO CHEESE AND, LIKE --
I WAS, LIKE, CHEESING SO HARD
AND LIKE JUST A LITTLE KID IN A
CANDY SHOP JUST BECAUSE I FELT
SO GOOD, LIKE, LEAVING YOU.
AND, LIKE, I JUST -- I DON'T
KNOW.
I JUST -- I'M BESIDE MYSELF, I'M
SO HAPPY.
>> I'M HAPPY TOO.
I'M, LIKE -- I THINK THIS IS,
TODAY -- WELL, THIS WHOLE WEEK
IS REALLY, LIKE, STARTING TO HIT
ME.
LIKE, IT'S --
>> THIS IS REAL.
>> OVER, BUT, LIKE, STARTING.
>> YEAH.
>> AND I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE THAT
WE ARE HERE, AND I'M SO GLAD,
BUT I DON'T -- THE UNKNOWN IS
AFTER THIS.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
AND WE'VE GOT -- I THINK IT'S
SOMETHING IMPORTANT FOR US TO
TALK ABOUT IS, WHAT IS LIFE
AFTER THIS?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU KNOW, I THINK FOR ME,
THERE'S NO DOUBT, I JUST WANT TO
RUN WITH THIS AND GO WHEREVER
LIFE TAKES US.
AND I JUST TRULY BELIEVE THAT I
CAN MAKE IT WORK FOR US NO
MATTER WHERE WE GO.
LIKE, YOU KNOW, I JUST KNOW THAT
WE CAN BE KICKASS IN OUR
MARRIAGE.
AND THE THINGS THAT MATTER TO ME
MOST ARE BUILDING A LIFE,
BUILDING A FAMILY.
AND, YOU KNOW, I WANT TO --
LIKE, MY KIDS AND YOU ARE, LIKE,
THE MOST IMPORTANT THING THAT
MATTERS TO ME.
I, LIKE -- LITTLE TIMMY YELLING
TO GETTING READY FOR BASKETBALL
OR GET READY FOR FOOTBALL
PRACTICE.
YOU KNOW, LIKE, THAT'S, LIKE,
THE STUFF, LIKE, I, LIKE, WANT.
THAT'S WHAT MATTERS TO ME.
>> THAT REALLY MAKES ME HAPPY
AND EXCITES ME.
>> AND I JUST -- THESE FEELINGS,
I DON'T EVER WANT TO LOSE THEM.
I DON'T WANT TO LET GO OF THEM.
AND I WANT TO CHERISH THEM
FOREVER.
'CAUSE YOU MAKE THE HAPPIEST
I'VE EVER BEEN, AND I DON'T EVER
SEE THAT CHANGING.
>> I AM SO LUCKY, AND I FEEL SO
LUCKY WHEN I THINK ABOUT A LIFE
WITH TYLER.
IT'S ALMOST LIKE HE IS -- HE'S
THAT PERFECT GUY.
WHAT'S UPSTAIRS, TYLER?
THE ONE THAT YOU WANT TO
INTRODUCE TO EVERYBODY THAT YOU
KNOW.
LIKE, "HERE'S MY HUSBAND,
TYLER."
>> HOW'S MY DESIGN?
>> PRETTY GOOD.
>> YEAH.
I DIDN'T DO IT.
>> I KNOW HE WOULD PROTECT ME,
KEEP ME SAFE, AND WE WOULD HAVE
THE SWEETEST FAMILY, CUTEST
LITTLE BABIES.
TYLER MAKES ME FEEL SO SPECIAL
AND SO LOVED.
I DON'T WANT HIM TO LET GO OF
ME.
LIKE, I COULD SEE BEING IN HIS
ARMS FOREVER.
♪
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> WELL, ALL RIGHT, EVERYTHING
IS LOOKING REALLY GOOD FOR
TYLER, BUT HANNAH HAS ONE LAST
DATE WITH JED THAT COULD CHANGE
EVERYTHING.
WHO WILL HANNAH CHOOSE AND WHAT
WILL HAPPEN AFTER WE STOP
FILMING.
I CAN TELL YOU IT IS AN ENDING
THAT NO ONE EXPECTED, LEAST OF
ALL HANNAH.
IT MAY NOT BE THE FAIRY TALE SHE
WAS EXPECTING.
STICK AROUND, BECAUSE HANNAH
WILL BE BACK ON STAGE TO TALK
ABOUT IT WHEN THE SEASON FINALE
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> WELCOME BACK TONIGHT ONE OF
OUR EPIC 2-NIGHT LIVE FINALE,
HANNAH HAD AN EPIC DATE WITH
TYLER, BUT HER NEXT DATE WITH
JED COULD CHANGE EVERYTHING.
WILL SHE MAKE THE RIGHT CHOICE?
LET'S FIND OUT.
♪
>> I HAD MY LAST ONE-ON-ONE WITH
TYLER YESTERDAY, AND IT WENT
AMAZING.
COULDN'T HAVE GONE BETTER.
BUT I HAVE MY LAST ONE-ON-ONE
WITH JED TODAY, AND I'M ANXIOUS.
THE LAST TIME WE WERE TOGETHER,
MEETING MY FAMILY DIDN'T GO LIKE
WE HOPED.
HEY.
AND IT'S BEEN SOMETHING THAT
I'VE BEEN REALLY CONCERNED
ABOUT.
I HAVE TO BE ABLE TO MAKE MY
DECISION FOR TOMORROW AND MY
FUTURE.
[LAUGHS]
WELL, TODAY IS A DAY TO
CELEBRATE ALL THAT WE'VE BEEN
THROUGH, AND WHAT BETTER WAY TO
DO IT THAN ON THE WATER HERE IN
GREECE?
SO LET'S DO IT.
>> LET'S DO IT.
♪
OH, MY GOSH.
>> NO WAY.
>> THIS IS REALLY COOL.
IT'S SO BEAUTIFUL.
>> ISN'T IT?
>> THIS IS FRICKIN' SWEET.
IS THIS REALLY ROCKY OR IS IT
JUST ME?
OH, MY LEGS ARE SHAKING.
LIKE, THIS WAS SUPPOSED TO BE A
SEXY DAY AND WE'RE BOBBING AND
WEAVING ON --
>> OH, HERE IT GOES.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> UP.
OH, I SEE SOME TREACHERY UP
AHEAD.
I SEE SOME TREACHEROUS SEAS.
>> OH, MY GOD, I'M GOING TO DIE!
I DON'T KNOW IF I LIKE ALL THESE
ROCKY WATERS.
UGH.
OKAY, [BLEEP] ME.
THIS SUCKS.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH.
>> BAD?
JUST -- I'M GOING TO GET SICK.
I WAS REALLY EXCITED ABOUT TODAY
WITH JED OUT ON THIS BOAT, BUT
I'M JUST TRYING TO KEEP BACK IN
MY BREAKFAST.
THIS IS NOT HOW THIS WAS
SUPPOSED TO GO.
UGH.
I ALSO DON'T FEEL THAT GREAT
BECAUSE OF THE UNCERTAINTY OF
EVERYTHING.
'CAUSE PEOPLE VOMIT WHEN THEY
GET NERVOUS, YOU KNOW?
>> MM-HMM.
>> THAT MAKE YOU NERVOUS EVER?
>> CONSIDERING ALL OF THE
THINGS, ALL THE VARIABLES IN
THIS, I'VE JUST BEEN REALLY JUST
EXCITED.
THIS IS THE MOST NERVOUS THAT
I'VE FELT PROBABLY.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> IT'S JUST A HEAVY WEEK.
>> AS OF RECENT, JUST THIS WEEK,
YOU MEAN?
>> MM-HMM.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
ME TOO.
IT'S PROBABLY THE MOST NERVOUS
I'VE BEEN.
>> YEAH.
I MEAN, I'VE THOUGHT ABOUT IT
A LOT.
AND AS SURE AS I AM ABOUT US, IT
IS STILL HARD TO KNOW THAT THERE
IS SOMEONE ELSE HERE AND THERE
ARE OTHER FEELINGS STILL
FLOATING.
>> YEAH.
>> AND THERE IS A CHANCE THAT IT
COULDN'T BE ME.
>> MM-HMM.
>> AND THAT'S JUST THE TRUTH,
AND I KNOW THAT.
AND FEELING LIKE YOUR DAD DIDN'T
BELIEVE IN ME, THAT'S WHAT
REALLY JUST KIND OF --
>> IT BOTHERED ME TOO.
>> BUT I JUST DON'T THINK HE
UNDERSTANDS, LIKE, THE OTHER
STUFF THAT I DO.
LIKE, I DIDN'T GO INTO, LIKE,
VAST DETAIL.
BUT IT'S NOT LIKE I ONLY KNOW
HOW TO DO MUSIC, YOU KNOW?
>> YEAH.
I THINK IT'S JUST THE
UNCERTAINTY OF IT.
>> I MEAN, AT THE END OF THE
DAY, LIKE, REALLY, I WAS SAD.
IT REALLY MESSED WITH MY HEAD.
BUT THEN WHEN I THOUGHT ABOUT
IT, AND I KIND OF CAME TO THE
CONCLUSION THAT IT DIDN'T CHANGE
THE WAY I FEEL ABOUT YOU AT ALL.
>> MM-HMM.
>> IT JUST WAS HARD BECAUSE I
JUST SO BADLY WANTED THEM TO BE
LIKE, "OH, YEAH, THERE IT IS."
LIKE, YOU KNOW?
>> MM-HMM.
♪
YOU KNOW, IT'S JUST REALLY
SETTING IN THAT I GET ENGAGED
TOMORROW, AND I'M FREAKING OUT
AND NERVOUS AND SUPER ANXIOUS
BECAUSE THE END IS SO NEAR.
AND I DON'T REALLY KNOW WHAT I'M
GOING TO DO.
I'M SORRY.
I'M -- I'M NOT MAD AT YOU OR
ANYTHING.
IT'S JUST WHEN I GET, LIKE,
SICK, I'M, LIKE, VERY --
>> I'M LITERALLY THE SAME.
>> LIKE...
[GROANS]
I HAVE TWO REALLY STRONG
RELATIONSHIPS AND TWO REALLY
GREAT GUYS, BUT I AM SCARED AND
I AM SAD ABOUT HAVING TO BREAK
SOMEBODY'S HEART TOMORROW, AND
IT COULD BE HIS.
♪
[KNOCKS]
>> HELLO.
>> HI.
>> COME ON IN.
>> HOW ARE YOU?
>> GOOD, HOW ARE YOU?
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> YOU LOOK NICE.
>> YOU TOO.
>> I HAVE A LOT TO FIGURE OUT
TONIGHT.
>> WELCOME.
>> I AM CONCERNED, AND I AM
CONFUSED AND CONFLICTED IN MY
HEART BETWEEN TWO MEN, AND I
NEED TO HAVE MORE CLARITY AND
REALLY USE TONIGHT TO SEE IF
THAT IS JED OR IF IT'S NOT.
>> I'M JUST GOING TO GO AND
APOLOGIZE IN ADVANCE FOR TONIGHT
'CAUSE THAT'S JUST ME, BUT I'M
DOING THE BEST I CAN, BECAUSE --
>> I AM TOO.
ME AS WELL.
>> I FEEL VERY, LIKE -- I FEEL
ANXIOUS.
>> YEAH.
>> JUST WITH EVERYTHING.
LIKE, JUST, LIKE, TODAY, AND I
WAS SAD THAT YOU WERE SEASICK,
BUT YOU CAN'T HELP THAT.
AND I KNOW THAT IT'S MORE THAN
THAT, ESPECIALLY WITH, LIKE,
WHAT'S GOING ON, BUT I JUST WANT
YOU TO KNOW THAT, LIKE -- I
JUST CANNOT IN ANY PART OF
MYSELF PICTURE MY LIFE WITHOUT
YOU AT THIS POINT.
>> I FEEL VERY LOVED BY YOU, BUT
I KNOW MY DAD WAS SO SKEPTICAL
OF THE MUSIC THING AND HOW THAT
WAS STABLE FOR FAMILY AND FOR
SUPPORTING ME IN YOUR LIFE.
>> I KNOW THAT.
>> AND SO, YOU KNOW THAT IF IT
IS US, I AM A DREAMER AND I HAVE
PASSIONS AND I WANT TO WORK WITH
THOSE.
IT'S JUST FINDING THE BALANCE.
AND, I MEAN, YEAH, IS IT SCARY
THAT WE ARE BOTH LIKE THAT?
YEAH, IT IS.
BECAUSE THERE HAS TO BE SOMEBODY
THAT WILL HAVE TO SACRIFICE AT
POINTS FOR THE OTHER PERSON.
AND I'VE DEFINITELY THOUGHT
ABOUT THAT.
>> I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW THAT,
THROUGH WHATEVER LIFE WOULD
THROW AT US, NO MATTER WHAT, I
WANT TO STEP UP TO THE PLATE AND
DO ABSOLUTELY EVERYTHING I CAN
FOR YOU AND TO LOVE YOU.
I WANT, MORE THAN ANYTHING, TO
TAKE CARE OF YOU.
I WANT TO BE THERE FOR YOU
THROUGH THICK AND THIN, AND I
FEEL LIKE, WITH YOU, I FEEL LIKE
I CAN DO ANYTHING.
I FEEL LIKE SPENDING FOREVER
WITH YOU, JUST -- I'VE NEVER HAD
IT MAKE SENSE OF ANYONE
SERIOUSLY.
LIKE, I'VE NEVER EVEN CONSIDERED
IT.
>> YOU DON'T THINK IT'S JUST
BECAUSE OF THIS THOUGH?
I'M SORRY.
I JUST AM FREAKING OUT A
LITTLE.
>> I KNOW.
I KNOW.
I -- I WOULD'VE LOVED YOU.
I DON'T CARE WHERE YOU WOULD BE
ON THIS PLANET, IF I WOULD HAVE
MET YOU OUTSIDE OF THIS
ANYWHERE, I WOULD'VE LOVED YOU.
I JUST MEAN IT WITH EVERY PIECE
OF ME, EVERY CELL, AND I JUST
WANT THAT FOREVER.
♪
>> I HAVE A TOUGH DECISION
TOMORROW.
IT'S EMOTIONAL WATCHING SOMEBODY
AND FEELING SOMEBODY LOVE YOU SO
MUCH.
[EXHALES]
>> SEE YOU TOMORROW.
♪
BUT AFTER TONIGHT AND JUST
THINKING ABOUT THIS WEEK, TYLER
AND JED AND THIS WHOLE
EXPERIENCE, I DON'T KNOW THAT I
HAVE THE CLARITY THAT I NEED FOR
TOMORROW AND A PROPOSAL.
I'M A LITTLE CONFUSED ABOUT WHAT
I WANT TO DO, AND I DIDN'T THINK
I WOULD BE IN THIS POSITION.
JUST THINKING ABOUT TYLER AND
JED, SO MANY FEELINGS ARE IN
EACH RELATIONSHIP.
I KNOW THAT I AM LOVED DEEPLY BY
BOTH MEN.
I KNOW THAT I'LL BREAK SOMEONE'S
HEART TOMORROW.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> WOW.
IT WILL HANNAH GET THE HAPPY
ENDING SHE DESERVES OR WILL IT
BE THE MOST SHOCKING FINALE IN
"BACHELORETTE" HISTORY THAT
MIGHT LEAVE ALL OF BACHELOR
NATION IN TEARS?
HANNAH IS WITH ME.
YOU WANTED TO SAY SOMETHING
HEADING INTO TOMORROW NIGHT?
>> YEAH.
SINCE THAT LAST DAY IN GREECE,
THE PAST COUPLE OF MONTHS HAVE
BEEN REALLY TOUGH AND EMOTIONAL.
I KNOW THERE ARE A LOT OF RUMORS
OUT THERE, AND HONESTLY,
TOMORROW NIGHT, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN.
BUT I HAVE A LOT OF QUESTIONS
THAT NEED TO BE ANSWERED, SO I
HOPE I'LL BE ABLE TO DO THAT.
>> THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> WE ARE GOING TO GET THOSE
ANSWERS TOMORROW NIGHT.
BACHELOR NATION, IF YOU'VE EVER
TAKEN MY ADVICE, HEAR THIS: GET
SOME REST TONIGHT BECAUSE
TOMORROW IS GOING TO BE UNLIKE
ANY FINALE WE HAVE SEEN BEFORE.
FOR HANNAH, FOR EVERYONE WHO HAS
BEEN A PART OF THIS ON, I'M
CHRIS HARRISON.
GOOD NIGHT, EVERYBODY.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
>> TOMORROW NIGHT, IT'S THE
SHOCKING CONCLUSION OF
"THE BACHELORETTE."
>> I CAN'T DO THIS.
I --
CAN YOU STOP THE CAR?
[GRUNTS]
I REALLY CAN'T DO THIS.
I JUST FEEL LIKE THIS EXPERIENCE
HAS BEEN TAKEN AWAY FROM ME.
HOW WOULD YOU EVER BE READY TO
BE ENGAGED?
LIKE, WHAT?
LIKE, I'VE BEEN DOING ALL THE
FREAKING STEPS AND I KNOW WHAT I
WANT.
>> THE DRAMATIC END TO HANNAH'S
SEARCH FOR LOVE TOMORROW NIGHT
ON "THE BACHELORETTE."